Guide to the Francis Griffith Newlands Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Francis Griffith Newlands papers
1869-1936
1899-1917
MS 371
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
44.75
(92 boxes)
The papers contain correspondence, speeches, reports, scrapbooks, and other material documenting the political career of Francis G. Newlands. The papers highlight Nevada Democratic and Silver Party politics and focus on Newlands's legislative programs on transportation, particularly railroads and inland waterways, interstate commerce, irrigation, flood control, land reclamation, currency and silver, conservation and forests, and tariffs. An addition to the collection contains over 600 personal letters to and from the Newlands family members, financial files, photographs, and topical files.
Newlands, Francis G. (Francis Griffith), 1848-1917
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Scrapbooks, 1887-1918, are available on microfilm HM 132.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of Edith Newlands Johnston, ca. 1932. Purchased from Barney Chapman, 2008 (Accession 2009-M-028).
Existence and Location of Copies
Scrapbooks, 1887-1918 are available on microfilm (13,270 frames on 15 reels, 35mm.) from Scholarly Resources, Inc., Wilmington, Delaware.
Arrangement
Arranged in three series and one addition: I. Correspondence and Papers, 1869-1917. II. Topical Files, 1869-1936. III. Scrapbooks, 1887-1918.
Scope and Contents
The Francis Griffith Newlands Papers are composed of correspondence, speeches, reports, scrapbooks, and printed material which document the political career of Francis G. Newlands. The papers highlight Nevada Silver and Democratic Party politics and focus on Newlands's legislative programs on transportation, particularly railroads and inland waterways, interstate commerce, irrigation, flood control, land reclamation, currency and silver, conservation and forests, and tariffs. An addition to the collection contains over 600 personal letters to and from the Newlands family members, financial files, photographs, and topical files.
In addition, the papers contain more than fifty scrapbook volumes of mounted clippings from 1887 to 1918. The scrapbooks, which contain the most complete and extensive record of Newlands's election campaigns and legislative programs, are arranged by topic and concern: Nevada politics, the Newlands Reclamation Act of 1902, railway legislation, irrigation, inland waterways, flood control, the Interstate Trade Commission, foreign affairs, the tariff, race problems, labor legislation, and the death of Senator Newlands. The scrapbooks were reproduced on fifteen reels of microfilm (HM 132) in 1982 after which the original volumes were discarded.
Biographical / Historical
Francis Griffith Newlands was born on August 28, 1848, in Natchez, Mississippi. He attended Yale College from 1867-1869, and graduated from Columbian College (George Washington University) in 1869. He received an honorary degree (M.A.) in 1901. He moved to San Francisco and practiced law in California (1870-1888). Newlands moved to Nevada in 1888 and won election to the House of Representatives (1893-1903). He subsequently served Nevada as U.S. Senator (1903-1917). Newlands died on December 24, 1917.
Select List of Correspondents
Adams, Brooks 1848-1927
Adams, Henry Carter 1851-1921
Adams, Jewett W 1835-1920
Adams, Samuel 1871-1935
Adee, Alvey Augustus 1842-1924
Ailes, Milton Everett 1867-1925
Alexander, Joshua Willis 1852-1936
Andrews, George 1850-1928
Anthony, Susan Brownell 1820-1906
Arnold, Joseph Addison 1857-
Ashbrook, William Albert 1867-1940
Ashurst, Henry Fountain 1874-
Bacon, Augustus Octavius 1839-1914
Bailey, Joseph Weldon, Jr. 1892-1943
Baker, Newton Diehl 1871-1937
Ballinger, Richard Achilles 1858-1922
Bankhead, John Hollis 1842-1920
Bard, Thomas Robert 1841-1915
Barrett, John 1866-1938
Barrows, Samuel June l845-1909
Bartholdt, Richard 1855-1932
Bartine Horace Franklin 1848-19l8
Bartlett, George Arthur 1869-
Bates, Arthur Leban 1859-1934
Beall, Jack (James Andrew) 1866-1929
Bell, Theodore Arlington 1872-1922
Belmont, Perry 1851-1947
Bennet, William Stiles 1870-
Bennett, Charles, Goodwin 1863-1914
Bien, Morris 1859-1932
Bingham, Henry Harrison 1841-1912
Black, John Charles 1839-1915
Boardman, Mabel Thorpe -1946
Borah, William Edgar 1865-1940
Bourne, Jonathan, Jr. 1855-1940
Bowers, George Meade 1863-1925
Bowman, Charles Calvin 1852-1941
Boyle, Emmet D(erby) 1879-1926
Bradley, William O'Connell 1847-1914
Brady, James Henry 1862-1918
Brandegee, Frank Bosworth 1864-1924
Breazeale, Phanor 1858-1934
Bristow, Joseph Little 1861-1944
Broussard, Robert F. 1864-1918
Brown, Horris 1863-1912
Brownlow, Walter Preston 1851-1910
Bryan, William Jennings 1860-1925
Bukeley, Morgan Gardner 1837-1922
Bullitt, William Christian, Jr. 1891-
Burkett, Elmer Jacob 1867-1935
Burleson, Albert Sidney 1863-1937
Burnham, Henry Eben 1844-1917
Burrows, Julius Caesar 1837-1915
Burton, Theodore Elijah 1851-1929
Butler, Marion 1863-1938
Byrns, Joseph Wellington 1869-1936
Callaway, Oscar 1872-1947
Callbreath, James Finch 1858-1940
Camden, Johnson Newlon 1865-1942
Caminetti, Anthony 1854-1923
Capper, Arthur 1865-1951
Carey, Joseph Maull 1845-1924
Carnegie, Andrew 1835-1919
Carter, George Robert 1866-1933
Carter, Thomas Henry 1854-1911
Cary, William Joseph 1865-1934
Chamberlain, George Earle 1854-1928
Chilton, William Edwin 1858-1939
Church, Denver Samuel 1866-1952
Clapp, Moses Edwin 1851-1931
Clark, Champ 1850-1921
Clark, Edgar Erastus 1856-1930
Clark, William Andrews 1839-1925
Clements, Judson Claudius 1846-1917
Coady, Charles Pearce 1868-1934
Cockrell, Francis Marion 1834-1915
Colt, LeBaron Bradford 1846-1924
Colquitt, Oscar Branch 1861-1940
Colton, George Radcliffe 1866-1916
Cook, George Washington 1851-1916
Cortelyou, George Bruce 1862-1940
Corthell, Elmer Lawrence 1840-1916
Coxe, Frank Morrell 1844-1916
Crane, Winthrop Murray 1853-1920
Crawford, Coe Isaac 1858-1944
Cresson, W(illiam) Penn 1873-1932
Cross, Wilbur Lucius 1862-1948
Crosser, Robert 1874-1957
Culberson, Charles Allen 1855-1925
Cullom, Shelby Moore 1829-1914
Curry, Charles Forrest 1858-1930
Curtis, Charles 1860-1936
Daniels, Josephus 1862-1948
Davenport, James Leroy 1845-1914
Davies, Joseph Edward 1876-1958
Dennett, Fred 1863-1928
Davis, Arthur Powell 1861-1933
Depew, Chauncey Mitchell 1834-1928
Dewey, Henry Sweetser 1856-
Dick, Charles William Frederick 1858-1945
Dickerson, Denver S. 1872-1925
Dickinson, Jacob McCavock 1851-1928
Dickson, William Alexander 1861-1940
Difenderfer, Robert Edward 1849-1923
Dillingham, Willian Paul 1843-1923
Dixon, Joseph Moore 1867-1934
Doremus, Frank Ellsworth 1865-1947
Dubois, Fred Thomas 1851-1930
Du Pont, Henry Algernon 1838-1926
Dyer, Leonidas Carstarphen 1871-1957
Eagle, Joe Henry 1870-
Elkins, Davis 1876-1959
Estopinal, Albert 1845-1919
Ewing, Thomas 1862-1942
Fergusson, Harvey Butler 1848-1915
Ferris, Scott 1877-1945
Fisher, Irving 1867-1947
Fisher, Walter Lowrie 1862-1935
Fitch, Thomas 1838-1923
Fithian, George Washington 1854-1921
Fitzgerald, John Joseph 1872-1952
Fletcher, Duncan Upshaw 1859-1936
Flint, Frank Putnam 1862-1929
Foelker, Otto Godfrey 1875-1943
Foulkrod, William Wa1ker 1846-1910
Fowler, Charles Newell 1852-1932
Frazier, James Beriah 1856-1937
Frear, James Archibald 1861-1939
Frissell, Hollis Burke 1851-1917
Fulton, Char1es William 1853-1918
Gage, Lyman Judson 1836-1927
Gallinger, Jacob Harold 1837-1918
Galloway, Beverly Thomas 1863-1938
Gardner, Augustus Peabody 1865-1918
Garfield, James Rudolph 1865-
Garrison, Lindley Miller 1864-1932
Gibson, Paris 1830-1920
Gillespie. Oscar William 1858-1927
Glasgow, Arthur Graham 1865-1955
Glynn, Martin H. 1871-1924
Goeke, John Henry 1869-1930
Goldfogle, Henry Mayer 1856-1929
Gompers, Samuel 1850-1924
Goodwin, William Shields 1866-1937
Gore, Thomas Pryor 1870-1949
Gorman, Arthur Pue 1839-1906
Graves, Henry Solon 1871-1951
Griggs, James Mathews 1861-1910
Griggs, John William 1849-1927
Hale, Nathan Wesley 1860-1941
Hall, Luther Egbert 1869-1921
Hammond, John Hays 1855-1936
Hammond, Winfield Scott 1863-1915
Hardy, Rufus 1855-1943
Harris, William Julius 1868-1932
Hartwell, Alfred Stedman 1836-1912
Hay, John 1838-1905
Helm, Harvey 1890-1919
Helvering, Guy Tresillian 1878-1946
Henry, Robert Lee 1864-1931
Heyburn, Weldon Brinton 1852-1912
Hill, Frank Davis 1862-1912
Hilles, Charles Dewey 1867-1949
Hitchcock, Ethan Al1en 1835-1909
Hitchcock, Frank Harris 1869-1935
Hitchcock, Gilbert Monell 1859-1934
Hobson, Richmond, Pearson 1870-1937
Hollis, Henry, French 1869-1949
Houston, David Franklin 1866-1940
Houx, Frank L. 1860-
Hudson, Millard F. (only letters to pres.)
Hughes, Charles James, Jr. 1853-1911
Hughes, Louis C. 1844-
Hull, Cordell 1871-1955
Humphrey, William Ewart 1862-1934
Humphreys, Benjamin Crubb 1865-1923
Igoe, William Leo 1879-1953
Jackson, William Purnell 1868-1939
Jenkins, John James 1843-1911
Johnson, Albert 1869-
Johnson, Ben 1858-1950
Johnson, Charles Fletcher 1859-1930
Johnson, John Albert 1861-1909
Johnson, Tom Loftin 1854-1911
Johnston, Joseph Forney 1843-1913
Jones, Andrieus Aristieus 1862-1927
Jones, Wesley Livsey 1863-1932
Kalanianaole, Jonah Kuhio 1871-1922
Kendrick, John Benjamin 1857-1933
Kent, William 1864-1928
Kern, John Worth 1849-1917
Kitchin, William Walton 1866-1924
Knowland, Joseph Russell 1873-
Knox, Philander Chase 1853-1921
Lafean, Daniel Franklin 1861-1922
Lafferty, Abraham Walter 1875-
LaFollette, Robert Marion 1855-1925
LaFollette, William Leroy 1860-1934
Landis, Charles Beary 1858-1922
Lane, Franklin Knight 1864-1921
Lane, Harry 1855-1917
Lansing, Robert 1864-1928
Lea, Luke 1879-1945
Lea, Blair 1857-1946
Lee, Robert E. -1916
Lewis, David John 1869-1952
Lewis James Hamilton 1863-1939
Lind, John 1854-1930
Linthicum, John Charles 1867-1932
Lippitt, Henry Frederick 1856-1933
Littlepage, Adam Brown 1859-1921
Lloyd, Jares Tilghman 1857-1944
Lobeck Charles Otto 1852-1920
Long, Chester Isaiah 1860-1934
McAdoo, William Gibbs 1863-1941
MacArthur, Arthur 1845-1912
McCleary, James Thomson 1853-1924
McCoy, Wa1ter, Irving 1859-1933
McCreary, James Bennett 1838-1918
McCumber, Porter James 1858-1933
McLean, George Payne 1857-1932
McReynolds, James Clark 1862-1946
Mac Veagh, Isaac Wayne 1833-1917
Madden, Martin Barnaby 1855-1928
Maginnis, Martin 1841-1919
Manderson, Charles Frederick 1837-1911
Marshall, William Louis 1846-1920
Martin, Anne Henrietta 1875-1951
Martin, Thomas Staples 1847-1919
Martine, James Edgar 1850-1925
Massey, William Alexander 1856-1914
Mercer, David Henry 1857-1919
Merriam, William Rush 1849-1931
Metcalf, Victor Howard 1853-1936
Meyer, George von Lengerke 1858-1918
Miller, Joaquin 1841-1913 (Miller, Cincinnatus Heine)
Milton, William Hall 1864-1942
Mondell, Frank Wheeler 1860-1939
Money, Hernando De Soto 1839-1912
Moody, Malcolm Adelbert 1854-1925
Moore, John Bassett 1860-1947
Moore, Joseph Hampton 1846-1950
Morgan, John Tylor 1824-1907
Morganthau, Henry 1856-1946
Morris, Robert page Walter 1853-1924
Murray, William Henry 1869-1956
Myers, Henry Lee 1862-1943
Needham, James Carson 1864-1942
Nelson, John Mandt 1870-
Nelson, Knite 1843-1923
Newberry, Truman Handy 1864-1945
Newell, Frederick Haynes 1862-1932
Newlands, Francis Griffith 1848-1917 (only letters to presidents)
Nixon, George Stuart 1860-1912
Noel, Edmund Favor 1856-1927
Norris, George William 1861-1944
Oddie, Tasker Lowndes 1870-1950
O'Gorman, James Aloysius 1860-1943
Oliver, George Tener 1848-1919
Olney, Richard 1835-1917
Osborne, Henry Zenas 1848-1923
Osborne, John Eugene 1858-1943
Overman, Lee Slater 1854-1930
Owen, Robert Latham 1856-1947
Page, Carroll Smalley 1843-1925
Page, Walter Hines 1855-1918
Pardee, George Cooper 1857-1941
Parsons, Herbert 1869-1925
Parker, Alton Brooks 1852-1926
Patterson, Thomas MacDonald 1839-1916
Paynter, Thomas Hanson 1851-1921
Pearre, George Alexander 1860-1923
Pearson, Richmond 1852-1923
Penrose, Boies 1860-1921
Perkins, George Clement 1839-1923
Piles, Samuel Henry 1858-1940
Pinchot, Gifford 1865-1946
Pittman, Key 1872-1940
Platt, Orville Hitchcock 1827-1905
Poindexter, Miles 1868-1946
Pomerene, Atlee 1863-1937
Quézon, Manuel Luis 1878-1944
Raker, John Edward 1863-1926
Ransde1l, Joseph Eugene 1858-1954
Redfield, William Cox 1858-1932
Reed, James Alexander 1861-1944
Reinsch, Paul Samuel 1869-1923
Richards, William Alford 1849-1912
Rixey, John Franklin
Roberts, Edwin Ewing 1870-1933
Robinson, Joseph Taylor 1872-1937
Rodey, Bernard Shandon 1856-1927
Roosevelt, Theodore 1858-1919
Root, Elihu 1845-1937
Rowe, Leo Stanton 1871-1946
Ryan, Thomas 1837-1914
Sabath, Adolph Joseph 1866-1952
Sadler, Reinhold 1848-1906
Sanders, Jared Young 1869-1944
Saulsbury, Willard 1861-1927
Scrugham, James Graves 1880-1945
Shafroth, John Franklin 1854-1922
Shaw, Leslie, Mortier 1848-1932
Sheppard, Morris 1875-1941
Sherman, James Schoolcraft 1855-1912
Shively, Benjamin Franklin 1857-1916
Simmons, Furnifold McLendel 1854-1940
Smith, Charles Emory 1842-1908
Smith, Ellison DuRant 1866-1944
Smith, George Otis 1871-1944
Smith, Herbert Knox 1869-1931
Smith, Hoke 1855-1931
Smith, John M. C. 1853-1923
Smith, John Walter 1845-1925
Smith, Mark Aurelius 1851-1924
Smith, Sylvester Clark 1858-1913
Southard, James Harding 1851-1919
Southwick, George N. 1863-1912
Spalding, George 1836-1915
Sparks, John 1825-1908
Stephens, William Dennison 1859-1944
Stewart, William Morris 1827-1909
Stimson, Henry Lewis 1867-1950
Stokes, Anson Phelps, Jr. 1874-1958
Stone, William Joel 1848-1918
Sutherland, George 1862-1942
Swanson, Claude Augustus 1862-1939
Taylor, Benjamin Irving 1877-1946
Taft, William Howard 1858-1929
Talbott, Joshua Frederick Cockey 1843-1918
Teal, Joseph Nathan 1858-1929
Teacher, Thomas Chandler 1858-1945
Thomas, Charles Spalding 1849-1934
Thompson, Carmi Alderman 1870-1942
Thompson, William Howard 1871-1928
Thornton, John Randolph 1846-1917
Tillman, Benjamin Ryan 1847-1918
Tongue, Thomas H. 1844-1903
Townsend, Charles Elroy 1856-1924
Townsend, Edward Waterman 1855-1942
Turnbull, Robert 1850-1920
Underwood, Oscar Wilder 1862-1929
Untermyer, Samuel 1858-1940
Van Duzer, Clarence Dunn 1866-l947
Vardaman, James Kimble 1861-1930
Wade, Martin Joseph 1861-1931
Walcott, Charles Doolittle 1850-1927
Walsh, Thomas James 1859-1933
Wanger, Irving Price 1852-1940
Warburg, Paul Moritz 1868-1932
Warner, Adoniram Judson 1834-1910
Warner, Vespasian 1842-1925
Warren, Francis Emroy 1844-1929
Washington, Booker Taliaferro 1859-1915
Waskey, Frank Hinman 1875-
Watson, Clarence Wayland 1864-1940
Webb, Edwin Yates 1872-1955
Weisse, Charles Herman 1866-1919
Weller, Luman Hamlin 1833-1914
Wheeler, Nelson Platt 1841-1920
Whitacre, John Jefferson 1860-1938
White, Francis (Frank) Shelley 1847-1922
Whyte, William Pinkney 1824-1908
Wickersham, George Woodward 1858-1936
Wiley, William Ha1sted 1842-1925
Williams, John Sharp 1854-1932
Willson, Augustus Everett 1846-1931
Wilson, James 1835-1920
Wilson, William Bauchop 1862-1934
Wilson, Woodrow 1856-1924
Withycombe, James 1854-l919
Wood, Leonard 1860-1927
Wooten, Dudley Goodall 1860-1929
Worcester, Dean Conant 1866-1924
Works, John Downey 1847-1928
Wynn, William Joseph 1860-1935
Yánes, Francisco Javier 1861-1924
* The following people have been removed from the blue file list and Catalogued:
Brandeis, Louis Dembits 1856-1941
Burbank, Luther 1849-1926
Butler, Nicholas Murray 1862-l947
Low, Seth 1850-1916
Wythe, Frederick S.
Additional Correspondence
Abbott, Ernest Hamlin 1870-1931
Abbott, Frederick H. 1872-1932
Adams, James B.
Adams, Romanzo 1868-1942
Aleshire, James Buchanan 1856-1925
Alexander, Moses 1853-1932
Allen, Sherman 1875-1938
Anderson, Frank Bartow 1863-1935
Anderson, Hendrick Christian
Armstrong, William Jackson 1841-
Ashley, George Hall 1866-1951
Atherton, George w 1837-1906
Austin, Oscar Phelps -1933
Babcock, James E.
Babcock Kendric Charles 1864-1932
Bacon, Edward Payson 1834-1916
Bain H(arry) Foster 1872-1948
Baldwin, Albertus Hutchinson 1865-
Baldwin, A(rchibald) Stuart 1861-1922
Baldwin, Elbert Francis 1857-1927
Ballard, Marshall
Barker, Wharton 1846-1921
Barnes, William 1824-1913
Barrett, Nathan F.
Barstow, George Eames 1849-1924
Bates, Lindon Wallace 1858-l924
Bshrman, Martin 1864-1926
Bell, J(ames) Franklin 1856-1919
Belmont, August 1853-1924
Bemis, Edward Webster 1860-1930
Bernheimer, Charles L. 1864-1944
Bingham, Ernest L.
Blount, James Henderson 1869-1918
Blue, Rupert 1868-1948
Blue, Victor 1865-1928
Boardman, Harold Sherburne 1874-
Borglum, Gutson (John Gutzon de la Mothe) 1871-1941
Bowman, John Gabbert 1877-
Boyd, James T.
Boyd, D. Knickerbacker 1872-1944
*Brandeis, Louis Dembitz 1856-1941
Brandon, Thomas A.
Britt, James Jefferson 1861-1939
Brodigan, George
Brooks, Sidney 1872-
Broward, Napoleon Bonaparte 1857-1910
Brown, Herbert Daniel 1870-
Brown, Hugh Henry 1872-
Bruce, Charles Morelle 1853-1938
Brunner, Arnold William 1857-1925
Bryan, Enoch Albert 1855-1941
*Burbank, Luther 1849-1926
Burrell, David James 1844-1926
*Butler, Nicholas Murray 1862-1947
Cabell, Royal Eubank 1878-1950
Cable, Benjamin Stickney 1872-1915
Cable, Benjamin Taylor 1853-1923
Calhoun, Patrick 1856-1943
Campbell, Helen Stuart 1839-
Campbell, William R.
Carpenter, Fred Warner
Carroll, (Alexander) Mitchell 1870-1925
Carson, John Miller 1838-1912
Caston, William
Cattell, Edward James 1856-1938
Chamberlain, Eugene Tyler 1856-1929
Chambers, William L.
Cheney, Agro E. 1854-
Chittenden, Hiram Martin 1858-1917
Choate, Joseph Hodges 1832-1917
Clark, Frank Sylvester 1868-1958
Clarke, Albert 1840-1911
Clarke, Sir George Sydenham 1848
Clexton, Philander Priestly 1862-1957
Clayton, Bertram Tracy 1862-1918
Clem, John Lincoln 1851-1937
Cleveland, Abner Coburn 1839-1903
Cleveland, Frederick Albert 1865-1946
Cobb, John Candler 1858-1933
Codman, Charles Russell 1829-1918
Colcord, Roswell Keyes 1839-1939
Cole, Nathan, Jr. 1860-1921
Coleman, Benjamin Wilson 1869-1939
Collier, David Charles 1871-1934
Conant, Charles Arthur 1861-1915
Cooley, Lyman Edgar 1850-1917
Corbin, Henry Clark 1842-1909
Crocker, William Henry 1861-1937
Crowder, Enoch Herbert 1859-1932
Crosier, William 1855-1942
Curtin, J. B.
Davis, Robert Courtney 1876-1944
Dawe, G(eorge) Grosvenor 1863-1948
Dekalb, Courtenay 1861-1931
Dekay, Charles 1848-1935
Delavan, D(avid) Bryson 1850-1942
Dennis, John Hancock
Dennis, Samuel K. 1874-1953
Devine, Edward Thomas 1867-1948
Dole, Charles Fletcher 1845-1927
Dolf, Thomas
Dougherty, Hugh 1844-1925
Doyle, John T. 1819-1906
Doyle, R.
Dunningan, John Sullivan 1835-
Durand, E. Dana
Dyer, Francis John 1864-1924
Easley, Ralph Montgomery 1856-1939
Eastman, John Coates 1862-1925
Eberhardt, Adolph Olson 1870-
Edmonds, Richard Hathaway 1857-1930
Edwards, Clarence Ransom 1860-1931
Elliot, Charles Gleason
Ellis, L. A.
Ely, Robert Erskine 1861-1948
Evans, Henry Clay 1843-1921
Ewing, Thomas
Fairchild, David Grandison 1869-
Fairchild, George Winthrop 1854-1924
Fairweather, John
Falkner, Roland Post 1866-1940
Farrar, Edgar Howard 1849-1922
Farrington, Edward Silsby 1856-1929
Fayant, Frank H. 1876-
Ffoulke, Charles Mather 1841-1909
Field, Carter 1885-1957
Finch, James D.
Fitch, Charles Hall 1854-
Flower, Frank Abial 1854-1911
Ford, Tirey Lafayette 1857-
Fowler, Benjamin Austin 1843-1921
Freedlander, Joseph Henry -1943
French, Daniel Chester 1850-1931
Furst, Clyde (Bownan) 1873-1931
Gibson, Edgar J.
Gilbert, Cass 1859-1934
Gilder, Joseph B. 1858-1936
Glass, Franklin Potts 1858-1934
Goodwin, Elliot H 1874-1931
Goodyear, C. P.
Gore, James Howard 1856-
Goudy, Franklin Curtis -1924
Goulder, Harvey Danforth 1853-1928
Grandfield, Charles Paxton 1861-
Grant, Madison 1865-1937
Gray, E(dward) (Dundas) McQueen 1854-
Gregory, Thoman Watt 1861-1933
Grunsky, Carl Ewald 1855-1934
Haggard, Sewell 1879-1928
Hall, William Hammond
Hammerling, Louis Nicholas 1874-1935
Hangar, G Wallace William 1866-1935
Harlan, James S. 1861-1927
Harr, William R. 1872-1950
Harries, George Herbert 1860-1934
Harvey, George (Brinton McClellan) 1864-1928
Haupt, Lewis Muhlenberg 1844-1937
Haworth, Erasmus 1855-1932
Hays, Willet Martin 1859-
Head, Franklin Harvey 1835-1914
Heard, Dwight Bancroft 1869-1929
Heath, Perry Sanford 1857-1927
Hellman, Isaias William 1842-1920
Henderson, Charles Richmond 1848-1915
Hendrick, Archer Wilmot 1871-1937
Henry, Bayard 1857-1926
Henshaw, Frederick William -1929
Henshaw, Henry Wetherbee
Hepburn, A(lonzo) Barton 1846-1922
Hermann, Binger 1843-1926
Herrin, William Franklin 1854-1927
Hill, John Wesley 1863-1936
Hines, Walker Downer 1870-1934
Hodges, LeRoy 1888-1944
Hodghead, Beverly Lacy 1865-1928
Hollander, Jacob H. 1850-1930
Holmes, Joseph Austin 1859-1915
Holmes, William Henry 1846-1933
Hooker, Arthur
Hopkins, Archibald 1842-1926
Houston, Herbert Sherman 1866-1955
Howe, Frederic Clemson 1867-1940
Hrdlicka, Alea 1869-1943
Hsing, Hwang
Humphrey, Charles Frederick 1844-1926
Hurley, Edward Nash 1864-1933
Huskey, H. W.
Ingersoll, Colin Macrae 1858-1948
Jaegers, Albert 1868-1925
James, Edmund Janes 1855-1925
James, Francis Bacon 1864-1897
James, George Wharton 1858-1923
Jenkins, Charles Francis 1865-1951
Jenks, Jeremiah Whipple 1856-1929
Jennings, Hennen 1854-1920
Johnson, Charles Freeman
Johnson, Emory Richard 1864-
Johnson, Robert Underwood 1853-1937
Jones, John E. 1872-
Jones, Richard Lloyd 1873-
Kavanaugh, William Kerr 1860-1932
Kavanaugh, William Marmaduke 1866-1915
Kellar, Philip R.
Kelliher, E. A.
Kellogg, Arthur Piper 1878-1934
Kellogg, Paul Underwood 1879-1958
King, Cora (Smith) 1867-1939
King Clyde Lyndon 1879-1937
King, William Rufus 1864-1934
Kluttz, Whitehead 1881-
Knaebel, Ernest 1872-1947
Knapp, Martin Augustine 1843-1923
KruttsChnitt, Julius 1854-1925
Kyle, Matthew
LaFarge, Christopher Grant 1862-1938
Laughlin, James Laurence 1850-1933
Law, Herbert Edward 1864-
Lay, Julius Gareche 1872-1939
Laylin, Lewis Cass -1923
Lee, William Granville 1859-1929
Leighton, Marshall Ora 1874-1958
Leland, Henry Martyn 1843-1932
Letcher, Marion 1872-1948
Lindley, Curtis Holbrook 1850-1920
Lindley, Hervey 1854-1929
Loeb, William 1866-1937
Logan, Albert J. 1857-1934
Loomis, Francis Butler 1861-1948
*Low, Seth 1850-1916
Lynch, Robert Newton 1875-1931
McAllister, Hall
Mac Beth, Ravenel
McCarthy, Charles 1873-1921
McClatchy, Charles Kenney 1858-1936
McClatchy, Valentine Stuart 1857-1938
McClure, Samuel Sidney 1857-1949
McCombs, William Frank 1875-1921
McCormick, Ruth (Hanna) 1880-
McCraney, H. A.
McFarland, J(ohn) Horace 1859-1948
McGee, W. J. 1853-1912
McGinty, George Banks 1878-1937,
McIlhenny, John A.
McIntyre, Frank 1865-1944
Mackenzie, A(lexander) 1844-1921
Mack, Norman Edward 1858-1932
Mager, William A.
Manning, Vannoy Hartrog 1861-1932
Manson, William O.
Marble, John Hobart 1869-1913
Marburg, Theodore 1862-1946
Marks, Marcus M. 1858-1934
Marsh, Benjamin C.
Marshall, Leo Carroll 1879-
Marshall, Louis 1856-1929
Matheson, William John -1930
Mauran, John Lawrence 1866-1933
Maxwell, George Hebard 1860-1946
Mayhugh, John S.
Mead, Elwood 1858-1936
Means, Thomas Herbert 1875-
Machlin, Leila 1874-1949
Meritt, Edgar Briant 1874-
Meriwether, Colyer -1920
Merriam, James Fiske 1845-1918
Marshon, Ralph Davenport 1868-1952
Millar, Alexander Copeland 1861-1940)
Miller, Adolph Caspar 1866-1953
Mills, Darius Ogden 1825-1910
Mitchel1, Guy Elliott 1870-1939
Moffett, Samuel Erasmus 1860-1908
Moore, Charles 1855-1942
Moore, Charles Arthur -1914
Moore, Charles Brainard Taylor 1853-1923
Moore, Charles Cadwell 1868-1932
Moore, Edward Bruce 1851-1915
Moore, Willis L(uther) 1856-1927
Morawetz, Victor 1859-1938
Morris, Frank Hubbard 1851-1900
Morrison, Frank 1859-1949
Morse, Edwin Kirtland 1856-1942
Moseley, Edward Augustus 1846-1911
Mullgardt, Louis Christian 1866-
Murray, Laurence O. 1864-1926
Mussey, Ellen Spencer 1850-1936
Myrick, Herbert 1860-1927
Neale, Walter 1873-1933
Needham, Charles Willis 1848-1935
Newlands, Edith McAllister
Newlands, James Jr.
Newlands, John
Newlands, Margaret A.
Newlands, Mary R.
Newman, Edwin A.
Newton, Byron Rufus 1861-1938
Noreross, Frank Herbert 1869-
North, Simon Newton Dexter 1849-1924